Ah, there you are, Mr. Lydon.
See you found the place okay.
It's nice to meet you.
Full disclosure,
we're not turnkey yet.
And I'm in big trouble if anyone finds out
I met you here.
But brochures couldn't
do this justice.
Am I right?
It's a work-in-progress
but that's why now's
when you get in
put your own stamp on it.
It's a killer view, right?
That's no...
"Look out! No!"
"Hurry!"
Yeah! You are going down, yo!
Okay, one more.
Uh, do you...?
Do you do realize, this is just a game.
I'm not competitive,
I just like to win.
Okay.
Oh wait, you know what? That...
That's cheating.
- Now that, that's...
- No spinning.
- Okay.
Yeah, there's spinning
in Chicago.
Woo!
Oh! There it goes.
Down the... Oh!
- Did that hurt?
- Yeah. A lot.
Did that hurt? All right.
I'm sorry. Is everybody here
watching the man
get beat by the girl?
- Guys?
- Yeah?
Can I close out this check?
My shift's about to end.
- Oh, yeah.
- One second, one second, one second.
- Okay. Hands off. Half-time.
- Okay.
One...
- Oh!
- Two... Oh!
Three!
Yes!
I'm gonna give you
some advice.
Never play Foosball
with a woman
that's raised three brothers.
- Thank you. It's exhausting.
- "Killing 2 FBI agents and 1 civilian"
"as they exited their car."
"In addition
to the two F.B.I. agents"
"a third victim, Edward Hu,
was on his way to testify today"
"in the high-profile murder trial
against Kelvin Bittaker."
"Bittaker is currently being
held on suspicion of murder"
"of A.U. scholarship student
Jamie Owen."
"Owen, from San Diego, California"
"was allegedly beaten to death
last month by Bittaker"
"after a dispute in a bar."
Can we get some
chicken wings?
Sure. We may have to
get them to go.
Can we get some chicken wings
to go, please?
- Yeah.
- "charges of first degree murder."
"Several witnesses in the bar claimed"
- "Mr. Bittaker appeared intoxicated..."
- Hey, boss.
"and had to be restrained
several times"
- "from becoming violent."
- All right, we'll be right there.
- We need to go. Now.
- Yeah.
- Uh, 86 the wings!
- Sure.
Thank you. Sorry.
Jane, Lisbon.
You recall Agent Spackman,
Dallas FBI.
He called us in on this one.
Agent Spackman.
Ah, good to see you.
I missed that face.
Lisbon. Jane.
We got four murders
in under three minutes.
29-year-old realtor,
67-year-old copy store owner
and two FBI agents.
Good men. Good family men
with, uh, young kids.
No security cameras,
no fingerprints.
Guy was in and out
like a ghost. Yeah.
The murder victim
Edward Hu?
He was the key witness
in a murder investigation
of one Kelvin Bittaker.
He beat a guy to death
over a spilled drink.
The family has been
of interest
to the Dallas FBI
for some time.
Their import-export
car warehouse is a front.
This murder case? This is just
a thin edge of the wedge.
Now, the hope here is to use
Kelvin's conviction
to take the whole family down.
Kelvin might be looking
at the needle
which might make him
more pliable.
Now how said the hope is,
not was
from which I surmise that you
have another witness
- to the murder?
- We do.
A young woman.
Young mother, actually.
If we can convince her
to testify after today
and if we can keep her alive.
You think the Bittakers have
a hit on her also?
That'd be a pretty bold
move at this point.
You can count on it.
This woman's testimony is
enough to bring them down.
If Kelvin goes to jail
he's gonna take the whole
family with him.
The young woman,
Lily Stoppard
is scheduled to testify
in two days time.
With a hit man of this caliber
we've been asked to come
and join the investigation.
Three perfect shots
from close to a thousand yards.
Not many snipers can
make hits from that distance
with that kind of accuracy.
- That should narrow it down, right?
- I wish.
Truth is, the shooter
could have been anybody.
Now, these Bittakers,
they can choose
any number of their contacts
to call in a hit.
Shooter could be
any nationality
- he could be any age...
- Nah, it's a regional guy.
And here we go.
Yeah. Local boy
with a sweet tooth
for powdered sugar beignets. See?
And, uh, they...
They shook hands, obviously.
How do we know that the, uh
victim wasn't holding
the beignet, Jane?
No! He's trim, he's spruced.
He's on the job.
He's not a pastry buff.
Doesn't mean that
the shooter's regional.
A lot of people like beignets.
Oh, I would argue that a lot
of people don't even know
what beignets are, Spackman.
- But I will concede you that point.
- Oh, thank you.
And I will focus on
who hired him
and what Kelvin did to that
boy from San Diego.
I'm guessing the Bittakers
have very little tolerance
for outsiders.
So if they ordered this hit
it would have been somebody
they were comfortable with.
Yeah, someone from down home.
All right.
So we'll run the profiles.
And, Jane, the last remaining
witness that we have
Lily Stoppard?
She's in HQ
under high security right now.
Spackman would like you
to talk to her.
Me? Why?
Because she might be reluctant
to testify
and we could do
with a little charm.
- A little charm?
- Yeah.
I don't know if I should be
insulted or, uh, flattered.
Well, whatever works.
- A little bit of both.
- Okay.
I don't see what
the difference is.
You couldn't protect
the other guy.
Matthew. Let's just
hear them out.
- Mrs. Stoppard.
- Lily.
Lily. Now you will continue to
receive our full protection
and I can assure you that
every conceivable effort
will be made to protect you
and your family.
But it's your choice.
Up to you.
Door's open.
Then no.
- Matt.
- No, this is nuts.
Why should you risk your life
for these people?
And what about our baby?
He needs you.
Are you even thinking
about him?
Of course
I'm thinking about him.
But I'm also thinking about
somebody else's child, too.
That poor kid.
Jamie Owen didn't even
fight back.
I mean, he couldn't.
"It was brutal."
"I knew right away he was dead."
"I didn't know what to do.
I was scared."
So I just stayed in my car and...
You called the cops. You did
your duty. That's enough.
We've got a baby at home,
and he's only 6 months old.
I don't understand how I'm
the only one who gets that.
Mr. Stoppard, I can
assure you, we, we...
We understand your concerns.
And they're pretty
darned reasonable.
Thank you. Finally.
What's your baby's name?
Henry. After Matt's dad.
Henry. Ah, that's a good
strong name.
I hate to talk to you
about doing the right thing.
Doing it is the easy part.
Knowing what it is
is tough.
And let me guess. You know
what the right thing to do is.
No, no, I don't, Matthew.
But, um, I'm gonna ask you this.
In years from now when, uh
you tell Henry this story.
How will it go?
Did the three of you take
an evil killer off the street
or did you play it safe?
Is Henry's birthright
gonna be one of proud bravery
or sensible caution?
Tough call.
Nice work.
I thought you were
blowing it back there.
Yeah, nice work. You better
look after that woman.
Hey, we will.
You have my word.
I don't want your word.
I want her safe.
Kelvin Bittaker, Supervising Agent
Dennis Abbott.
Sit down.
My mama taught me
never talk to strangers.
Four good people are dead.
Don't test my patience.
Well, a lot of good people
are dead, hoss.
It's the way of the world.
Sit down.
So, what four people
we talking about?
Outside of the courthouse
this morning
two FBI agents, a realtor
and Edward Hu.
You're kidding me.
Hallelujah.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
Bittaker didn't know about
the murders before I told him.
He didn't order the hits himself.
Well, we got the profiles
on the other family members
- from the Dallas field office.
- All right, well, tell me about them.
Middle brother Ethan
has a record.
He also has some health issues.
Caleb's only 19
but according to Spackman
that kid's a real smart-ass.
He's being groomed
for something bigger.
Intel's a little sketchy
on the mom, Belinda.
Well, one of them must've
reached out to the hitman
to make the contract.
Yeah, but we don't know
which one or how.
Now Spackman's team has been
through all their phone records.
The family's been
wired up for months.
And I take it
they searched their computers.
No communication regarding
hits on a witness
no coded messages,
all clean as a whistle.
But they're not.
Why don't you go see the family?
Take Jane.
You got it.
Hey!
Who are you people?
How'd you get in here?
- Ethan Bittaker?
- Who wants to know?
FBI.
Uh, you can keep walking.
Gotta have an appointment.
Ma!
Ma! The feebs are here!
Oh, Ethan!
Please don't be rude.
How can I help you, agents?
We wanna talk to you
about four dead men
and the hit you have out
on Lily Stoppard.
Whoa! That's quite a leap.
How did we arrive there?
What four dead men?
Who's Lily?
Mrs. Bittaker,
you are a fabulous liar.
Sir, please don't mock me.
My oldest boy is in jail
for a crime he didn't do
and Ethan here has terrible
health problems.
Honey, you know I love you.
And we're just making it
hand-to-mouth
until this whole mess
is cleared up.
And, and I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Really? Because these
Ferraris and Phantoms
don't say
"hand-to-mouth" to me.
It's like a master class
in dishonesty.
You can't just bust in here
and accuse us of assassinations
or whatever the hell else.
- That's harassment.
- Yeah.
- Where's your warrant?
- Ethan. Ethan, I, I understand.
Being a Bittaker middle child
can't be easy
and I, I sympathize
but you really do have to take control
of these attention issues.
Mrs. Bittaker, where have you
been for the last three days?
Beauty shop.
Oh, head shot! Sweet!
Oh, check your left, Funguy.
Left! Sniper's on you!
Boom! Cal Da King
crushes again!
- Kneel before me and die, scum!
- This is Caleb?
He's the one
with the smarts, huh?
This is a private office.
You gotta get out of here.
What's that game he's playing?
It looks fun.
- Come on.
- I'll go.
- Get out of here!
- I'm going.
Did you break her yet?
Ah, okay. Let's go. Shall we?
Pleasure meeting you,
Mrs. Bittaker.
You have a wonderful family.
You must be very proud.
You can sneer at me
all you like.
I will. Thank you. Hey.
Lay off the antidepressants.
They're making you slow.
And you're still not happy,
are you?
Don't ever make me
tell you this again.
Do not play this game
when people are here.
Got it?
Here we are.
War Lord 3.
Hold on.
"Cal Da King" you say.
I will run the logs.
Yep. He's in a tournament circle.
Caleb's gamer tag
is "Cal Da King."
And from there
they can talk to anyone
- anywhere, anytime?
- If they're in your circle.
Well, bingo. That's how they
communicated with the hit man.
Through the game.
There's a thousand people
in Cal Da King's circle
and conversations aren't logged.
There's no way
to narrow it down.
Is there some kind of
ranking, uh, thing?
Of course.
That's the point.
So if someone entered
the War Lord circle
wo wasn't really there
as a gamer, then...?
- They would suck, basically.
- Okay, let's run an ID trace
on the bottom three
cyber warriors on that list.
Of course.
Just in time.
Ballistics came up with a match.
We have a suspect.
He has two previous hits
with the same make of bullet.
Yeah, you were right, Jane.
This guy's definitely
from the region.
Either that or he's been
operating here
for the last few years.
Downloads from
the realtor's smartphone
says that he was meeting
someone named Lydon.
Which is obviously an alias.
Now the problem is we got
no fingerprints on this guy.
Got no facial recognition,
no ID, nothing.
Did we verify Lydon's
connection to the Bittakers?
Not so far.
Normally, with a guy like Lydon
there'll be a go-between involved.
An intermediary who sidesteps
hard or cyber links.
Now the problem is tracking it.
There's too many potential
methods of communication.
They could be using anything.
They could be using dating sites
or a dead email address.
Hell, they could even use
the old-school meet on the street.
And we don't have time
to go through all of...
Sorry to interrupt.
Jane, I've got three names
for you.
Ah, the Bittaker-Lydon connection.
The bottom three are Juniesdad
- 62-year-old male from Nova Scotia.
- Nah.
OldGalsRule, 57-year-old
female from the UK.
CountMeIn66, 35-year-old
female from Louisiana.
- Her. Definitely her.
- Excuse me, Jane.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Well, I highly doubt your
go-between lives in Nova Scotia
or the UK for that matter
so I'm gonna vote on
Miss Louisiana.
"Hey, Wylie.
What've you got?"
"Her real name
is Peg Bailey from Lafitte"
"and get this. Her ex used to work
as an enforcer for the Bittakers."
"Thanks, Wylie."
Looks pretty deserted.
No, I think there's
someone here.
We have to assume there is, okay?
All right, here's the plan.
Lisbon and I are
gonna check it out.
Jane, you stay.
- Ken, really? Stay?
- Listen to me.
For all we know, this lady's
just bad at video games
all right? And I don't wanna
go upsetting the locals.
Uh, I'm happy to wait here.
I'm not your dog.
You jackass.
Anybody here?
Wait here.
I'll check around the back.
Hey! Ho!
There's someone there.
Excuse me, sir, does
Peg Bailey live here?
Oh, uh, Peg's not here.
We're with the FBI.
I'm Agent Lisbon.
This is Patrick Jane.
Who are you?
Austin. You come a long way.
Uh, hope it's nothing serious
that brought you down.
I'm Peg's cousin Billy.
Wh, what's the issue, ma'am?
Can we come in?
It's a bit of a mess
but if you want.
I can't say
when she'll be back.
You can tell your friend
he can come in.
Jane, stay with him.
Okay. Spackman.
Spackman? Look at me.
- In, one, two.
- Spread it wide open.
Out, one, two.
Good job keeping his heart rate
down before we got here.
Probably kept him
from bleeding out.
Take care, Spackman.
Hey, boss, they're bringing
Spackman to a hospital
in Port Arthur now.
But they have stabilized him.
"I don't know. I think so.
He's gonna be okay."
Uh, one more thing.
We found a picture of Lily Stoppard
on Peg Bailey's computer.
I want you two
to get back here ASAP.
"We'll put you in a room
with a forensic sketch artist."
All right, we'll get there
as soon as we can.
Problem is, we got
too good a look at him.
Well, how is that a problem?
Well, this is who we saw.
Lydon knows we got
a good clear look at his face.
He, he'll never be that
good old boy again.
Wylie, can you take this
and generate
disguise variations on it?
Hair length, glasses, beard,
that kind of thing?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
So we'll see what that turns up.
You wanted to see me, boss?
- The arrogance of it all.
- Normally is.
Witnesses, our people,
now this Peg Bailey?
Jane figures they communicate
with her through video games.
And just like that she's dead.
God, I wanna crush
these people.
Yeah? Me too.
Ethan Bittaker has kidney
dialysis four times a day.
I'm thinking he might be
a tad fragile
with his health issues and all.
And he has 38 months left
on his parole.
You want me to lean on him?
Let's both go lean on him.
Let me go. Let me go. Mom!
- What's going on? What are you doing?
- Stop it. Stop it. Mom.
What's it look like we're doing?
Well, it looks like you're arresting
a dangerous parole violator,
Agent Cho.
A parole violator?
What did I do?
Consorting with a known felon.
- Who?
- Kelvin Bittaker.
- That's... That's my brother.
- That's ridiculous.
Bad news, Ethan. Jail time
- for the rest of your sentence.
- Mom. Mom.
Wait, he has to be on dialysis
in less than an hour.
Oh. Wow.
Well, that is a problem.
Oh, well, how's this?
We'll take his IV pole with us.
Oh, just while we hold you.
Now, I can't say
what's gonna happen
- when he goes back to the pen.
- What's going on?
Care to illuminate me, Agent?
Supervising Agent Dennis Abbott.
My.
I'm gonna lay this out in words
that are designed to resonate.
You're gonna call off
the hit on Lily Stoppard.
You will call it off.
And you will deliver us Lydon.
Or I won't be able to answer
to your son's well-being.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm truly lost
in this conversation.
You wanna call my bluff?
Well, do it. Please.
Because while Ethan suffers,
or whatever happens to him
it'll be on you.
He's nothing to me.
But he's not, is he?
He's not nothing to you.
You're a lawman
a supervising agent
and he is a citizen.
Sure, you may make him
unhappy or uncomfortable
but you're not gonna
let him die.
You're too damn ethical
for that.
They don't know me,
do they, Cho?
- No.
- I think I do.
And I'm gonna bet
my son on it.
Nice chatting with you, ma'am.
Okay, go get that damn pole.
One, two, three.
Bang, bang.
I've set it for slideshow.
Let me know if you need more.
- "Approaching Alpha..."
- Whoa, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Hold on.
Sorry. That's not it.
Impressive.
- Uh, can you print those out?
- Sure.
And make sure you send them
to the hotel Lily's staying at
as soon as you can.
Nice job.
Of course, Battlefield
was always my favorite
- but that's just me.
- Battlefield?
Oh. Yeah. You know,
the big boy game?
But, hey, some people just can't
handle that kind of pressure.
Oh, you mean that
little simple game
with just a couple hotkeys
to worry about?
Left trigger, right trigger, win.
Oh, it won't be so simple
when I no-scope you
for a team wipe.
Listen, Vega, I think a little
1-V-1
might clear this whole thing up.
- Pistols only.
- Any day. Any time.
The hit is still in play.
We'll hold Ethan for 24 hours
but Lydon has been a step
ahead of us the whole way.
We have to get ahead now.
Lily's testifying tomorrow.
First thing in the morning, yeah.
Well, Lydon probably already
scoped out her hotel
so we'll change her.
Uh, Lily's safe as long as she's
in her hotel room, yeah?
Yes. She has full protection
from the car to the courthouse.
But not en route to the car.
- No.
You... You wanna stay
ahead of Lydon?
You leave Lily where she is.
We make our own plan.
Okay, which is what?
The general who chooses
the field of battle wisely
wins before the fighting starts.
Okay. I'm listening.
"Lobbies are porous.
Multiple ways in and out."
"Lots of camouflage too."
"We'll need all hands on deck."
"The moment we leave her room,
it's on."
Bang.
"Lydon will take advantage
of small spaces and passageways."
"Areas not seen by the public.
He'll use it all."
Bang.
"We can't leave the husband behind.
We'll have to position him too."
"He'll have an exit plan
well in place."
"We're gonna want one too."
- Bang.
Bang.
By my count,
I've been shot six times.
Seven, but, uh...
Okay, that's good.
I got it. Thank you.
- Hi.
- You all right?
Uh, yeah. I'm fine.
Everything's gonna be okay tomorrow.
You know that, right?
We know what we're doing.
It's a good plan.
It's a really good plan.
He has a good plan too.
We're gonna be safe.
Someone could get hurt.
It's always dangerous.
This is different.
Everybody will be fine.
I promise.
We're all gonna be fine
if that's what this
insomnia is about.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm right
"everything's gonna be okay?"
No, it's what
the insomnia's about.
Come to bed.
Please. Come on.
All right.
Do you want me to sing you
the lullaby
I used to sing to my brothers
when they couldn't sleep?
Um, I really, uh
- don't wanna hear that.
- Okay.
"Oh, we're halfway there"
"Oh, livin' on a prayer"
- "Take my hand and I'll..."
- Yeah.
"Make it I swear"
- Come on, sing.
- Oh, no.
"Oh, livin' on a prayer"
- "Take my hand and we'll make it, I swear"
- "Dear God, the pain"
Wylie's in position
in the van outside.
Okay, good.
Everyone should be
getting into place soon.
The only thing that we have
to do is run the timeline
with Lily and Matthew.
Uh, Vega, would you mind
getting them?
Did you confirm that
the monitors are up in the van?
Yes. Wylie was able to tap
into the hotel security system.
All the monitors in the van
are on live feed now.
Okay. Excellent.
Hey, Lily.
How you doing?
- Fine.
- That's good.
Matthew, holding up?
- Is it time already?
- No, not yet.
Lily's, uh, expected to be
in the courthouse
in a little under two hours,
so we'll leave in about an hour.
Matthew, we're gonna need
to get you into position
ahead of time before Lily
leaves the room.
The car will be in the garage
of the hotel.
The elevator goes directly
to them
but we do have
alternative routes
just in case
something happens.
Can you people guarantee
that this will work?
Today's plan has your wife's
safety as our only goal.
We don't know exactly
how this is gonna play out
but I can say that we've explored
every possible scenario
and we're prepared for it.
Well, thank you.
All of you.
Good. All right.
Vega? If you don't mind.
Hey.
If anything happens to her
today, you know
and I could have stopped it?
Matthew. Your wife wants to do this.
And we'll do everything
to keep her safe.
It was a good decision.
You need to trust her
on it, okay?
I'd like to run through
the schematics one more time.
I'm gonna take a...
Another quick look around.
- I'll be back very soon.
- Okay.
Okay, it's happening.
- What's happening?
- Smoke in the hallway.
- Smoke bomb?
- Yeah. Probably.
It's okay.
Everybody just stay back, okay?
All right?
It's a decoy.
He wants the chaos.
- We push on.
- Let's get into position.
The elevators are gonna get
shut down.
They do that in emergencies.
Okay, Jane, I need you to get
down to the van where Wylie is.
All right? Take the stairs.
Everybody, let's go.
Make your way to the exits.
This is an emergency.
You cannot go back to your room.
Make your way to the exits.
Everyone calm down.
Slow down. Take your time.
This is an emergency.
You cannot go back to your room.
Make your way to the exit.
Abbott and Magath are in
Lily's suite on monitor one.
All right.
So how do I talk to them?
Thank you. Abbott, it's Jane,
I'm in the van.
"All right, copy that."
"Lisbon and Cho are
in the bedroom with Lily."
Good. So everyone's
accounted for.
- Where's Vega?
- "I'm here. I'm in position."
Excellent. Everyone listen up.
Watch for emergency personnel.
Anyone in a uniform.
That's how Lydon's coming in.
"I left it up in my room.
I can't..."
"Make your way to the exit.
We are evacuating the building."
"Yeah, I left it up."
Make your way to the exit.
We are evacuating the building.
Stay calm. Everyone, everyone stay calm.
"Are you okay?"
Uh, you need to go now.
"Copy that.
We're moving out."
Are you good?
- I'm good.
- Let's go.
"This way."
Oh, what do we have here?
Is that him? Is that him?
"Hey, Lisbon."
"West stairwell
entering the 6th floor."
"Could be him dressed as an EMT."
- I got it.
- Uh, don't get too close.
Just try to confirm if it's him.
Jane, I got it.
Jane, I'm on the sixth floor now.
Yeah. Lisbon, it looks like he...
He may be at the other end.
"Keep going."
Ma'am, you okay?
No, I, I, I hurt my ankle.
- Which one is it?
- This one.
All right, we're gonna need you
to reach out here, okay?
You're gonna be okay.
Follow me.
"Jane, it's not him."
We're headed down
to the seventh floor.
Abbott, by no means
rushing you
but if things get tight,
we may have to rethink things.
Good to know
you're not rushing me.
Jane. The lights went out.
Yeah, I, uh, I saw that.
He is there. Be careful.
Help! Help me!
I've been shot!
- I got this.
- You got it?
- All right. I got it.
- There's a shooter in the hotel.
- He went downstairs.
- Okay, buddy. Hold on.
Oh... oh, tell them to be careful.
All right. Let me see
where you got hit.
- Elevator's in locked-down.
- All right, try the stairway.
Down!
Suspect is down.
We got an agent down,
service stairwell, seventh floor.
"Everyone all right?"
Jane. That's confirmed.
The target's secure.
Great work team.
"Did you get that, Lisbon?"
Lisbon, where are you?
Yeah. I got it. I'm here.
I'm just getting back
with the team.
It's good news.
Well, here we are. Cozy.
Lily Stoppard
took the stand today
testified against your son Kelvin.
We had a positive ID on Lydon
hard evidence against you
and your family
for five murders
and two attempted murders.
So now you want me
to crack?
Throw a child of mine
under the bus to save myself?
- No.
- Good. Because I won't.
Someone like you doesn't have
the faintest idea
about the love a parent
has for a child.
You're right. I don't.
But I'm guessing it's what Jamie
Owen's mom felt about him.
And the other five victims.
They had parents too.
No deals. No bargaining.
You're all gonna go down together.
It'll be a family trip.
Have you figured it out yet, Belinda?
How your never-miss hitman
missed so badly?
"But he was close too."
"But we knew that."
"That's why we moved Lily
out of harm's way"
"and subbed in one of our own"
right before his eyes.
Sometimes people just see
what they want to see.
I don't mean to gloat, but...
"Number of people remaining"
"in the benefits roll
after drawing conditions week"
"again shot up
by a hundred and eleven..."
Hey, Vega.
- You see this?
- What?
Oh, oh, sorry, sorry.
Not this.
I meant...
No way.
- Oh, it is so on.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
- You think?
Psh. I know.
- You are going down!
- Uh-uh.
- Stop! Ha!
- Won't happen.
- Hey, that's cheating!
- It's not.
- I am so going for you.
- It's not gonna happen.
- You are going down.
- You're gonna lose.
You ready? Ready?
There you are.
- Here I am.
- Yeah.
Uh, okay.
Uh, what's wrong?
Why? You must already know.
- Yeah. I, I took you...
- You took me off.
- Mm-hm.
- On purpose.
You knew that wasn't Lydon
on the sixth floor.
You had to have,
but you sent me there anyway.
Yeah, that's right.
- I wanted to protect you.
- Protect me?
- I'm an FBI agent. It's my job.
- Look, I know.
And... And I'm sorry, but...
But what?
You'd do it again?
Yeah. I...
Yep. Probably would.
- That's a problem.
- It's not a problem.
- Oh, really? A big one.
- No...
You can't do that. Okay,
you have to let me do my job.
- If you can't...
- Yeah, I understand.
If you can't... I don't know.
Like... How do we work together?
Well...
We work it out.